Ariel Cook

Web Developer

Phone: 619-455-9608 ~ Email: arielcook101014@gmail.com ~ Website: acookonline.com ~ LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/arielcook71 ~ Github: github.com/arielmks

Summary: A highly creative and detail oriented web developer, experienced with the development process. **Technical Skills:** Javascript, Reactjs, Redux, Nodejs, Express, C/C++, HTML5, CSS3, JQuery, MongoDB **Recent Projects**

Cargo Containers | https://cargocontainer1.000webhostapp.com

A responsive website for a cargo container sales company

- Utilized JQuery's slide show feature to display images of shipping containers for enhanced user experience.
- Incorporated JQuery SlickNav navigation for friendly mobile menu.
- Designed feature for printable and organized reports.

Motiv | https://motiv-fitness.herokuapp.com

A social networking web application that keeps track of user's progress related to fitness

- Created a full stack feature which allows the user to create fitness goals and monitor their progress.
- Implemented asynchronous methods for interaction between client and server side data.

Education

Los Angeles City College | LA HI-TECH Web Development Program 2018 | AA in Computer Science 2017 - Present Hack Reactor | Advanced Immersive Software Engineering, 2016

Coastline Community College | Associate of Arts in Social and Behavioral Science, 2014

Work Experience

PortAsia Cargo Management, August 2016 – present

Logistics Coordinator

- Communicate with shipping lines to determine item availability and assist with inventory control.
- Representative analyzing customer needs including quotes, modifications, and pricing structures.
- Coordinate with trucking companies to accommodate scheduling and delivery.

RealOfficeCenters, January 2015 – February 2016

Maintenance Supervisor

- Supervised a team of four workers to provide various maintenance duties for the upkeep of an office building.
- Provided security services during private events.

State of California - San Luis Obispo County

Maintenance Coordinator, November 2010 - November 2014

- Coordinated preventative and corrective maintenance tasks for eight manufacturing plants.
- Developed a software application in Microsoft Access with Visual Basic to automate work orders.

Graphic Designer, January 2006 - November 2010

- Designed and produced various printing products including magazines, catalogs, and posters.
- Worked with pressmen to ensure correct layout prior to production phase.

Volunteer Experience

The Francisco Homes, 2014 - present

- Tutor residents with basic computer skills, and assist with resume building.
- Provide transportation for various appointments.